In other words...
There's a guy that gathered
100 coins and got special powers,
he's incredibly powerful, and he's
protecting the coins around crash site.
That's right.
So, we've got to do something about him
if we want to snatch those coins, huh?
That's why we made this team.
Well, I don't care, as long as I get my cut.
Should be a fun way to kill some time.
By the way, Naoto...
You seem to know a lot about this guy.
Have you met him before or something?
He's Naoto and I's...
He's an old friend of ours.
"A few months earlier"
Aiko's been acting weird lately.
What do you mean?
You guys are a couple, right?
Did you get in a fight?
That's not what I meant.
We went and saw a movie together last week.
Then there's no problem, right?
I don't know, something just feels off.
Huh?
Sometimes, I feel like she's a different person.
What do you mean, "a different person"?
Nothing, never mind.
A lot has happened lately.
Hmm?
Sorry. Forget about it.
If you say so.
Aiko... I haven't seen her for a while.
Or the others, for that matter.
Yeah. Brings back memories, huh?
"Yamada Cram School"
Yamada Cram School...
Not like we did much cramming...
They called it a school,
but it was basically a place
for working parents to leave their kids.
Me, you, and Shuichi.
And Mrs. Yamada was still alive then, too.
Shuichi! It went over to you!
Aah!
Are you okay, Shuichi?
Yeah.
Shouldn't you guys be studying?
Relax, Kaito!
Let me see that, Shuichi.
You got it, Naoto!
Wait, I'll do it!
It'd be nice to see everyone again.
Huh?
You can get in touch with
everyone right? Okay then.
Kaito! It's been a while!
Still got that pretty face, huh?
And you're still as loud as ever, Aiko.
What's that supposed to mean?
Come on, Naoto!
You're my boyfriend; stand up for me!
Well, you do make a lot of noise.
What? You jerk!
She doesn't seem all that different.
Sorry we're late.
Wow, you're going for a top college, Shuichi?
You've got the skills to get
into any college, no sweat.
I'm not so sure...
Hey, what's up with Honoka? She's late.
Huh?
What?
Oh. You didn't hear about it...
Huh?
Honoka's dad got into some trouble
in Tokyo and was arrested.
What?!
Apparently, he killed someone.
I guess it was hard for
her around here, after that.
"You should die" "Get out"
"Demon" "You will pay"
I guess it was hard for
her around here, after that.
"You should die" "Get out"
"Demon" "You will pay"
She just kind of disappeared one day.
You're kidding...
Why didn't anyone tell me?
Sorry. I thought you hated gossip like that.
Hey...
Since we're all together,
why don't we go to karaoke or something?
What?!
Aiko...
Come on, come on! Let's go!
Let's go, Naoto!
It's not easy to say this, Kaito...
But I think you should try
to forget about Honoka.
She didn't say anything to us, either.
I don't think she wants us to look for her.
I know what Aiko said.
But I had to find out more.
After all the stuff happened with her dad,
Honoka was taken in by
some relatives in a nearby town.
She just up and disappeared one day.
Huh?
We reported it to the police...
But if you find her, could you tell her this?
Don't bother coming back here.
Hold on--
What happened? Where is she now?
There must be a clue somewhere...
Since we're all together, why don't
we go to karaoke or something?
The way she twirled her hair...
Honoka always did that!
What the hell is going on?!
Now that I think about it,
that was a weird thing to say.
But I think you should try
to forget about Honoka.
Aiko knows something.
Damn, I lost her.
Can I help you?
She's already gone home... Kaito.
Who are you...?
"Hotel Mythos"
An alien?
Why'd you bring us out here so late?!
I'm getting tired of having to do
this every time... but here's proof.
Wha--?!
We need to talk.
The Aiko we know now is a transformed Honoka.
Transformed? What the hell
are you talking about?!
Naoto, you noticed something was out of place.
That's why you mentioned it to me, right?
I turned Honoka into Aiko.
As thanks for this coin.
Coin?
Coins... Wishes...
Is it all true?
That was her wish.
She wanted to erase herself
and become someone else.
You got it, Naoto!
I am telling you because
I heard you were her friends.
I'd prefer you didn't make a big deal out of it.
If her story gets out,
people will probably come for me.
And then I will be forced to protect myself.
If it comes to that,
I can't say what might happen.
I don't get it...
Honoka is Aiko now...?
If that's all true, then where is the real Aiko?
Honoka was in love with you.
Aiko had everything that Honoka wanted.
She was taken in by her relatives
but was never accepted by them.
With the alien's help, she turned into
Aiko in attempt to gain all that Aiko had.
I can't believe Honoka would...
Is there any other way to explain it?
We can't go to the cops with the alien here.
But if Honoka did commit some crime,
she should pay for it.
We know the truth, and we spent time with them--
We're the only ones who can do this.
I don't know. Honoka was so kind,
I just can't believe she'd do it.
So then where is the real Aiko?
"Stay home! Bitch"
Stop it.
Huh?! Stop what?
It's too dangerous.
What are you saying, Naoto?
Your girlfriend isn't really your girlfriend!
I know that. But I stick by what I said.
What?!
What the hell do you know, anyway?
Honoka might be Aiko now,
but she's not causing any trouble.
What if we ignore the alien's warning
and something happens? What'll we do?
Nothing needs to change...
Just like normal... If we just stay quiet,
everything will stay the same.
--Naoto!
--I agree with Naoto.
Huh?
You do too, don't you Shuichi?
Right?
Yeah.
You guys...
Are you okay with how that ended?
I...
I think things should stay as they are.
If that won't hurt you... or the others... I...
Everything... will stay the same?
Going somewhere, Aiko?
Be careful, now!
Hmm? Is something wrong?
No. See you later.
Brings back memories, huh?
Was the building really this small?
It felt so much bigger back then.
We've all grown.
You're right. We're the ones that changed.
Is that where you buried Aiko?
Answer me. You're Honoka, aren't you?
How did you know?
Your twirling.
You always used to twirl your hair.
Just that was enough?
Honoka... Can't you go back
to who you used to be?
No.
I mean... She doesn't even exist anymore...
I see.
Elena... What's wrong?
They found Aiko's will.
It was written a while ago.
In Aiko's handwriting.
And it was addressed to Honoka.
It was addressed to Honoka?
That's right.
Honoka... didn't kill Aiko?
Right. The real Aiko killed herself.
But then...
Why did I kill Honoka?
Honoka...
Are you... sure?
That's what you said, right?
That you'd grant my wish?
I did... But...
So, I want you to turn me into someone else.
A very dear friend died.
Hey, what are you doing?!
A person with a strong sense of justice.
Seeing that kind of thing really pisses me off!
It's okay, there's no way I'll give in to them.
"Stay home! Bitch"
She was my best friend.
But...
"I'm sorry."
I couldn't save her.
It's not too late.
I'm the only one that knows she died.
She was really loved by everyone.
If she's gone, everyone will be sad.
But if I disappear, nobody will be sad.
Honoka...
That's not true.
I see. So that's it.
Naoto had somehow realized
that Aiko killed herself.
So did Shuichi and Elena.
They all thought it'd be fine
if everything wrapped up the way it was.
Nobody minded that Honoka disappeared.
I mean... She doesn't even exist anymore...
I see. That's why I killed her.
Because I couldn't just let Honoka disappear.
Because I was the only one
that didn't want her to disappear.
That's why I killed Honoka.
You can all disappear.
Kaito disappeared.
He disappeared?
"New Palace Pachinko"
Did you hear the rumor about the glowing girl?
Huh?
A glowing girl stands on
a path and asks "Who am I?"
If you can't tell her her name, you get erased.
You get erased?
What does it mean?
I don't know. But you guys met the alien
and heard about the coins, right?
It seems like something
crazy is happening in this town.
When we talked about it before...
If we just stay quiet,
everything will stay the same.
I pretended not to know. But that was a mistake.
This is my fault, too.
We've got to see!
If Kaito is plotting something,
then I'll use the coin's power...
"Yamada Cram School"
"Present Day"
Did you go to Yamada Cram School
when you were little?
I used to see you hanging out
with all your friends.
That's weird. I never hung out
with anyone at cram school.
Shuichi's past...
Shuichi? Where are you?
Can we meet up?
So, she did it after all.
What's going on?! Shuichi!
Clair. It's okay.
It's over.
Huh?
Why won't he...?
Hello?
Sorry to call you again. It's Yoshioka.
I need to talk to you.
"Episode 13: We Two Are One"